[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following animals is the least related to the octopus?", "correct_answer": "Eel", "incorrect_answers": ["Scallop", "Snail", "Clam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The division of a company or university that deals with software technology is often called the IT department. What does IT stand for?", "correct_answer": "Information Technology", "incorrect_answers": ["Inter-networking Technology", "Informatics and Technology", "Internet Technology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of accent do the Three Little Pigs from the Shrek movies have?", "correct_answer": "German accent", "incorrect_answers": ["French accent", "Russian accent", "Irish accent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ephebiphobia is the fear of youth.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As a general rule, the bigger a dog is the more it should be exercised (walks, playing fetch, etc.)", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The manatee is a marine mammal.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In April 2007 a new version of Blackjack was approved for playing in the U.S. state of Washington. What is it called?", "correct_answer": "Three Card Blackjack", "incorrect_answers": ["Pantoon", "Chinese Blackjack", "Multiple Action Blackjack"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Take love, multiply it by infinity and take it to the depths of forever and you still have only a glimpse of how I feel for you. (1998)", "correct_answer": "Meet Joe Black", "incorrect_answers": ["Moulin Rouge", "My Best Friends Wedding", "Message In A Bottle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Exactly half of the US states have an even number of letters in their name.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these pairs actor - western movie he has played in is wrong?", "correct_answer": "Liam Dunn - The Mark of Zorro", "incorrect_answers": ["Rock Hudson - Gun Fury", "Eli Wallach - The Magnificent Seven", "Lance Henriksen - Dead Man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The director, writer and star of the movie Facing the Giants is an associate pastor.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long does it take the Sun to rotate once upon its axis?", "correct_answer": "About 24 to 28 days", "incorrect_answers": ["The Sun does not rotate at all", "About 24 to 30 hours", "About once a year"]}]